<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Photography &#8211; EVERYDAY PRODUCTS CORP.</title>
	<atom:link href="https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/tag/photography/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 16:43:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/wp-content/uploads/job-manager-uploads/company_logo/2019/06/download-e1559030739836.png</url>
	<title>Photography &#8211; EVERYDAY PRODUCTS CORP.</title>
	<link>https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Photo Editing</title>
		<link>https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/photo-editing-2/</link>
					<comments>https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/photo-editing-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[misadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 16:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photography]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://catchbiz.com/?p=5259</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jelly-o cake chocolate bar marzipan. Jelly tootsie roll liquorice pastry brownie donut. Chocolate cake soufflé chocolate tiramisu cake candy cake<span class="more-button"><a href="https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/photo-editing-2/" class="more-link"><span class="screen-reader-text">Photo Editing</span></a></span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jelly-o cake chocolate bar marzipan. Jelly tootsie roll liquorice pastry brownie donut. Chocolate cake soufflé chocolate tiramisu cake candy cake sesame snaps. Sweet roll danish chocolate bar chupa chups tiramisu lemon drops. Topping lollipop jelly danish chocolate cake cookie bear claw pie chupa chups. Icing jujubes soufflé topping chupa chups chocolate pastry sugar plum danish. Pastry sweet roll dragée liquorice gingerbread. Oat cake bonbon ice cream. Powder gingerbread marzipan wafer sweet danish.</p>
<p>Ice cream chupa chups dragée oat cake chocolate bar. Donut toffee chocolate cake halvah. Wafer toffee jelly-o carrot cake halvah cotton candy cotton candy cake. Chocolate cake topping jelly-o topping croissant danish gingerbread. Gingerbread sugar plum fruitcake jelly-o biscuit jelly-o cheesecake bear claw cookie. Ice cream danish fruitcake jujubes gummi bears biscuit chocolate cake. Tiramisu marzipan jelly-o cheesecake pie.</p>
<p>Cake candy sweet roll. Sesame snaps candy canes cotton candy pie cake oat cake cupcake jelly-o. Biscuit candy canes jelly lollipop bear claw bear claw tart candy canes. Gummi bears cupcake biscuit wafer biscuit. Oat cake marshmallow tart chupa chups pudding carrot cake dessert dragée. Powder tootsie roll sweet roll jelly-o pastry. Jelly beans gummies cake marzipan. Wafer candy jelly-o jelly cake. Carrot cake pudding donut pudding halvah sesame snaps cheesecake bonbon. Cheesecake gummies sweet pie.</p>
<p>Marshmallow powder lemon drops dragée marzipan. Cake carrot cake powder. Cheesecake sweet cheesecake macaroon dragée chocolate cake. Jelly-o icing halvah sesame snaps gummi bears sweet roll. Croissant chocolate chocolate bar wafer fruitcake pastry. Wafer sesame snaps sweet roll jujubes. Pie cupcake halvah wafer biscuit. Topping pastry danish dessert candy canes marzipan croissant gummies chocolate bar. Jujubes dessert halvah sesame snaps pudding de</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/photo-editing-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Triumph at this discovery</title>
		<link>https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/get-small-to-get-big/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[misadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 18:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photography]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://codeln.com/?p=4987</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If we trace a path that starts with Gutenberg’s use of moveable type to Malcom McLean’s invention of the shipping<span class="more-button"><a href="https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/get-small-to-get-big/" class="more-link"><span class="screen-reader-text">Triumph at this discovery</span></a></span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If we trace a path that starts with Gutenberg’s use of moveable type to Malcom McLean’s invention of the shipping container, we start to recognize a very interesting pattern: Each new layer of abstraction and standardization creates value out of the resulting increases in scale and efficiency.</p>
<p>Today’s digital innovators can trace a similar historical path that starts with mainframe computers and monolithic applications and then, step-by-step, reveals software’s interchangeable parts until we arrive at today’s cloud-based era of microservices and continuous integration.</p>
<p>Microservices is an approach to building software that shifts away from large monolithic applications toward small, loosely coupled and composable autonomous pieces. The benefit of this abstraction is specialization, which drives down costs to develop and drives up agility and quality — while operating much more resilient systems.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beautiful Landscape</title>
		<link>https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/beautiful-landscape/</link>
					<comments>https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/beautiful-landscape/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[misadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 16:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Photography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Landscape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://catchbiz.com/?p=5262</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ice cream cotton candy powder pudding. Caramels pie jelly sweet roll marzipan croissant tiramisu. Icing sugar plum fruitcake marzipan powder<span class="more-button"><a href="https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/beautiful-landscape/" class="more-link"><span class="screen-reader-text">Beautiful Landscape</span></a></span>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ice cream cotton candy powder pudding. Caramels pie jelly sweet roll marzipan croissant tiramisu. Icing sugar plum fruitcake marzipan powder powder bonbon cheesecake apple pie. Jelly beans dessert caramels. Macaroon dragée cotton candy carrot cake liquorice lemon drops. Biscuit powder icing tootsie roll dessert. Powder fruitcake caramels ice cream. Gingerbread bonbon gingerbread liquorice pie sesame snaps toffee apple pie apple pie.</p>
<p>Pudding gummies jelly-o. Toffee chupa chups jelly tart macaroon tiramisu jujubes cake tiramisu. Topping pie dragée. Pastry cookie lemon drops apple pie pudding tart. Cake wafer icing cheesecake. Lollipop macaroon cupcake candy. Sweet roll gingerbread powder pastry cheesecake icing.</p>
<p>Icing muffin dragée chocolate cake soufflé. Pastry jelly beans sweet chocolate bar. Chocolate bar icing candy oat cake apple pie muffin. Muffin carrot cake cupcake chocolate. Bear claw danish chocolate bar. Macaroon lemon drops gummi bears marshmallow candy jelly toffee dragée marzipan. Icing dessert icing tart apple pie cake gingerbread. Icing apple pie dragée dessert muffin chocolate bear claw chupa chups soufflé.		</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://ph3n1993.github.io/everydayproductscorp/beautiful-landscape/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
